Guide to the Frank Moore Papers, 1971-2003 MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Printed Materials, 152367
  - Subseries E: Books, 152368
    - Ingholt, Harald Gandharan Art in Pakistan, 1957; 152465 (Box 36, Folder 1327)
    - Interchangeable photo-scrap album, undated; 152464 (Box 36, Folder 1328)
    - Japanese book unknown, undated; 152463 (Box 36, Folder 1329)
    - Jarman, Derek Queer Edward II, 1992; 152462 (Box 36, Folder 1330)
    - Jones, LeRoi The Dead Lecturer, 1964; 152461 (Box 36, Folder 1331)
    - Jones, Michael Wynn The Cartoon History of the American Revolution, 1975; 152460 (Box 36, Folder 1332)
    - Jug Bug: The Joy of Juggling, 1977; 152459 (Box 37, Folder 1333)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231855
    - Jung, Emma Animus and Anima with annotations, 1957; 152458 (Box 37, Folder 1334)
    - Justice, Donald Departures, 1973; 152457 (Box 37, Folder 1335)
    - Kandinsky, Wassily Concerning the Spirituality in Art, 1947; 152456 (Box 37, Folder 1336)
    - Kapplow, Hal and Bob Reisner Captions Courageous, or, Comments from the Gallery, 1958; 152455 (Box 37, Folder 1337)
    - Khayyam, Omar Rubaiyat, undated; 152454 (Box 37, Folder 1338)
    - Koch, Kenneth Wishes, Lies and Dreams: Teaching Children to Write Poetry, 1970; 152453 (Box 37, Folder 1339)
    - Langenscheidt's Universal Dictionary English-Italian and Italian-English, 1962; 152452 (Box 37, Folder 1340)
    - Lazarus, Richard Personality 2nd edition, 1971; 152451 (Box 37, Folder 1341)
    - Lebensztejn, Jean-Claude Malcolm Morley: Itineraries, 2001; 152450 (Box 37, Folder 1342)
    - Lee, Sherman E. The Sketchbooks of Hiroshige, 1984; 152449 (Box 37, Folder 1343)
    - Lord, Douglas Vincent Van Gogh Letters to Meile Bernard, 1938; 152448 (Box 37, Folder 1344)
    - Love Speaks its Name: Gay and Lesbian Love Poems, 2001; 152447 (Box 37, Folder 1345)
    - Lucas, E.V. A Wanderer in Paris, undated; 152446 (Box 37, Folder 1346)
    - Machiavelli, Niccolo The Prince and The Discourses, 1950; 152445 (Box 37, Folder 1347)
    - Mains, Geoff Urban Aboriginals: A Celebration of Leathersexuality, 1984; 152444 (Box 37, Folder 1348)
    - Manhattan Observed, undated; 152443 (Box 37, Folder 1349)
    - Maroc: Costumes, Broderies, Brocarts, undated; 152442 (Box 37, Folder 1350)
    - Mayer, Ralph The Artist's Handbook of Materials and Techniques, 1970; 152441 (Box 38, Folder 1352)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231863
    - McAlester, Virginia and Lee A Field Guide to American Houses, 1988; 152440 (Box 38, Folder 1353)
    - McDermott and McGough 1936, 1996; 152439 (Box 38, Folder 1354)
    - McDonald, Sterling Color Harmony with the McDonald Calibrator, 1949; 152438 (Box 38, Folder 1355)
    - Merrill, James A Different Person, 1993; 152437 (Box 38, Folder 1356)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art Greek and Roman Art, 1975; 152436 (Box 38, Folder 1357)
    - Modern Dreams with annotations, 1988; 152435 (Box 38, Folder 1358)
    - Moholy-nagy, Laszlo The New Vision and Abstract of an Artist, 1947; 152434 (Box 38, Folder 1359)
    - Morrisroe, Mark Mark Morrisroe, 1999; 152433 (Box 38, Folder 1360)
    - Museum of Modern Art Joseph Cornell, 1980; 152432 (Box 38, Folder 1361)
    - Nadeau, Maurice Histoire du Surrealisme, 1964; 152431 (Box 38, Folder 1362)
    - A New Guide to Rome, undated; 152430 (Box 38, Folder 1363)
    - New Year Pictures of Weifang, Shantung, 1978; 152429 (Box 38, Folder 1364)
    - New York City Landmarks, undated; 152428 (Box 38, Folder 1365)
    - O'Connor, Flannery The Complete Stories, 1979; 152427 (Box 39, Folder 1366)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231871
    - O'Doherty, Brian American Masters: The Voice and the Myth, undated; 152426 (Box 39, Folder 1367)
    - O'Hara, Frank The Selected Poems of Frank O'Hara, 1974; 152425 (Box 39, Folder 1368)
    - Oldenburg, Claes Drawings and Prints, 1969; 152424 (Box 39, Folder 1369)
    - Ouspensky, P.D. A New Model of the Universe, 1971; 152423 (Box 39, Folder 1371)
    - Pickvance, Ronald Van Gogh in Arles, 1984; 152422 (Box 39, Folder 1372)
    - de Pisis Opre su carta 1921-1952 with an essay by Francesco Gallo, biography by Claudia Gian Ferrari, 1984; 152421 (Box 39, Folder 1373)
    - Plato The Symposium, 1973; 152420 (Box 39, Folder 1374)
    - Plato The Symposium of Plato Translated by Suzy Groden, 1970; 152419 (Box 39, Folder 1375)
    - Porter: Art in its own terms with annotations, 1979; 152418 (Box 39, Folder 1376)
    - Ramakers, Micha Dirty Pictures: Tom of Finland, Masculinity and Homosexuality, advance, uncorrected proof, 2000; 152417 (Box 39, Folder 1377)
    - Ricardo, Jack Leathermen Speak Out, 1991; 152416 (Box 39, Folder 1378)
    - Ristat, Jean Le Parlement d'amour, undated; 152415 (Box 39, Folder 1379)
    - Ristelhueber, Sophie Beirut, 1984; 152414 (Box 39, Folder 1380)
    - Robertson, Bryan Jackson Pollock, 1960; 152413 (Box 40, Folder 1381)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231889
    - Rockman, Alexis Alexis Rockman, 1995; 152412 (Box 40, Folder 1382)
    - Rockman, Alexis Evolution, 1992; 152411 (Box 40, Folder 1383)
    - de Rola, Stanislas Klossowski The Golden Game, 1988; 152410 (Box 40, Folder 1384)
    - Roma, parte 2, undated; 152409 (Box 40, Folder 1385)
    - Romanesque Catalan Art, undated; 152408 (Box 40, Folder 1386)
    - Rombauer, Irma and Marion Rombauer Becker The Joy of Cooking with annotations, 1964; 152407 (Box 40, Folder 1387)
    - Saunders, E. Dale Mudra: A Study of Symbolic Gestures in Japanese Buddhist Sculpture., 1985; 152406 (Box 40, Folder 1388)
    - Savinio, 1990; 152405 (Box 40, Folder 1389)
    - Scudiero, Maurizio and David Leiber Depero Futurista dn New York, 1987; 152404 (Box 40, Folder 1390)
    - The Science of AIDS, 1989; 152403 (Box 40, Folder 1390)
    - Seraullaz, Maurice Degas: Women Dressing, 1958; 152402 (Box 40, Folder 1392)
    - Shaw, Albert A Cartoon History of Roosevelt's Career, 1910; 152401 (Box 40, Folder 1393)
    - Smith, Bradley Japan: A History in Art, 1964; 152400 (Box 40, Folder 1394)
    - Soby,James Thrall The Prints of Paul Klee, 1947; 152399 (Box 41, Folder 1395)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231897
    - Souls Grown Deep: African American Vernacular Art of the South [located in oversize box], 2000; 152398 (Box 41, Folder 1396)
    - Sparks, Esther Universal Limited, 1989; 152397 (Box 41, Folder 1397)
    - Steiner, Jorg and Jorg Muler. The Bear who wanted to be a Bear, 1976; 152396 (Box 41, Folder 1398)
    - Stein, Gertrude Picasso with annotations, 1959; 152395 (Box 41, Folder 1399)
    - Stevens, Wallace The Palm at the End of the Mind, 1972; 152394 (Box 41, Folder 1400)
    - Stout, Wesley W. A War Job "Thought Impossible", 1945; 152393 (Box 41, Folder 1401)
    - Styron, William Lie down in Darkness, 1969; 152392 (Box 41, Folder 1402)
    - Szarkowski, John The Photographer's Eye, 1966; 152391 (Box 41, Folder 1403)
    - Taschen, Benedikt Cheri Samba Postcard Book, undated; 152390 (Box 41, Folder 1404)
    - Therrien, Robert Polaroids Drawings, 1996; 152389 (Box 41, Folder 1405)
    - Tocqueville, Alexis Democracy in America, 1947; 152388 (Box 41, Folder 1406)
    - Tomkins, Calvin Dechamp: a Biography, 1996; 152387 (Box 41, Folder 1407)
    - Thompson, Mark Leather-Folk: Radical Sex, People, Politcs and Practice, 1991; 152386 (Box 41, Folder 1408)
    - Townsend, Larry The Leatherman's Handbook II, Updated Second Edition, 1989; 152385 (Box 41, Folder 1409)
    - A Treasury of Western Folklore, 1951; 152384 (Box 42, Folder 1410)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231905
    - Les Tres Riches Heures du duc de Berry, undated; 152383 (Box 42, Folder 1411)
    - Trinidad, David Three Stories, 1988; 152382 (Box 42, Folder 1412)
    - Trollope, Anthony Barchester Towers with annotations, 1983; 152381 (Box 42, Folder 1413)
    - Trungpa, Chogyam The Myth of Freedom and the Way of Meditation, 1976; 152380 (Box 42, Folder 1414)
    - Tsarouchis, Yannis Pientures, 1992; 152379 (Box 42, Folder 1415)
    - Tyler, Ron Visions of America, 1983; 152378 (Box 42, Folder 1416)
    - Valery, Paul Selected Writings, 1950; 152377 (Box 42, Folder 1417)
    - Walt Disney's Moving Picture Flip Book, undated; 152376 (Box 42, Folder 1419)
    - Watson, Steven Strange Bedfellows, 1991; 152375 (Box 42, Folder 1420)
    - Wilde, Oscar Plays with annotations, 1957; 152374 (Box 42, Folder 1421)
    - Winston, Leyland Queer Dharma: Voices of Gay Buddhists, 1998; 152373 (Box 42, Folder 1422)
    - Woolf, Virginia Mrs. Dalloway with annotations, 1953; 152372 (Box 43, Folder 1423)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042231913
    - Yeats, W.B. Selected Poems and 2 plays, 1962; 152371 (Box 43, Folder 1424)
    - Yoganada, Paramahansa The Law of Success, undated; 152370 (Box 43, Folder 1425)
    - Zhisui, Dr. Li The Private Life of Chairman Mao with annotations, 1994; 152369 (Box 42, Folder 1426)
- Oversize Materials: Series I, Notebooks, 152343
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series I: Notebooks
  - Notebook #4, 1974-1976; 152366 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Notebook #9, 1976; 152365 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Loose Items from Notebook #9, 1976; 152364 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Notebook #21, 1978; 152363 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #26, 1979-1980; 152362 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Notebook #27, 1979-1980; 152361 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Loose Items from Notebook #27, 1979-1980; 152360 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Notebook #28, 1978-1980; 152359 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Notebook #31, 1980; 152358 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #36, 1980-1981; 152357 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Notebook #40, 1981; 152356 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #41, 1981-1982; 152355 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Notebook #42, 1981-1982; 152354 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #43, 1981-1982; 152353 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Notebook #44, 1981-1982; 152352 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Loose items from Notebook #44, 1981-1982; 197080 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #51, 1982-1983; 152351 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Notebook #59, 1984-1985; 152350 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Loose Items from Notebook #59, 1984-1985; 152349 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #73, 1990-1991; 152348 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Loose Items from Notebook 73, 1990-1991; 152347 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #81, 1992-1995; 152346 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #87, 1996; 152345 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Notebook #96, undated; 152344 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Oversize Materials: Series II.A: Frank Moore Clippings, Exhibition Announcements, Press, etc., 152308
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series II.A: Frank Moore Clippings, Exhibition Announcements, Press
  - New York Arts Journal, 1978; 152342 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - PS1 Poetry Project, 1980; 152341 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Watercolor Show, 1980-1981; 152340 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Collaborative Show with George Negroponte, undated; 152339 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Broccoli, undated; 152338 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Beast: Animal Imagery in Recent Painting, 1982; 152337 (Folder 14 Right)
  - Collaboration with Jim Self at the Kitchen, undated; 152336 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Moulton-Splatter, 1986; 152335 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Crankhouse, 1988; 152334 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Center Exhibit, 1990; 152333 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Joffrey Ballet, 1991; 152332 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Certificate of Service, Volunteer Adult Services Administration, 1992; 152331 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - CFDA: Council of Fashion Designers of America, 1992; 152330 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Citation for Contribution to SAFE Portfolio, 1992; 152329 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Slow Art, 1992; 152328 (Box 69)
  - Henie-Onstad Kunstesenter Hovikodden, 1993; 152327 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Cure Project Art Show, 1994; 152326 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Interview Magazine, 1994; 152325 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Requested Documentation, 1995; 152324 (Box 69)
  - XXX Fruit, 1995; 152323 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Interview Magazine, 1996; 152322 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Group Show, includes Frank Moore's The Gambler, undated; 152321 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - OUT Magazine Art Calendar, 1997; 152320 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - "The Art of Being You", Interview Magazine Supplement, undated; 152319 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1999; 152318 (Box 69)
  - ArtForum, 2002; 152317 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Interview Magazine, 2002; 152316 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Frank Moore's Obituary, 2002; 152315 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Orlando Weekly, 2002; 152314 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Frank Moore: Between Life and Death, proofs, undated; 152313 (Folder 3 Right)
  - Genomic Issue(s), 2003; 152312 (Box 69)
  - Folder featuring "Wildlife Management Area" and Stretch", undated; 152311 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Hospital sign, undated; 152310 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Yosemite Color Copies, undated; 152309 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Oversize Materials: Series II.C: Frank Moore Administrative Files, 152305
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series II.C: Frank Moore Administrative Files
  - ArtForum, 1975; 152307 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Mousepad, 2002; 152306 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Oversize Materials: Series II.D: Other Artist Art Files, 152279
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series II.D: Other Artist Art Files
  - Callahan, Harry, undated; 152304 (Folder 13 Left)
  - Condo, George, undated; 152303 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - de Fazio, undated; 152302 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Ford, Walton, undated; 152301 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Frame, Allen, undated; 152300 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Futura 2000, undated; 152299 (Box 69)
  - Harte, Glynn Boyd, undated; 152298 (Box 69)
  - Lunch, Lydia, undated; 152297 (Box 69)
  - Mueller, Cookie, undated; 152296 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Nahas, Nabil, undated; 152295 (Folder 6 Left)
  - Torres, Felix Gonzalez [located in map case], undated; 152294 (Folder 2)
  - Sarfati, Patrick, undated; 152293 (Folder 14 Left)
  - Self, Jim, 1981-2000; 152292 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Self, Jim- Cunningham Studio, undated; 152291 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Self, Jim at Jacob's Pillow, undated; 152290 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Jack, undated; 152289 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Sperone, Gian Enzo, undated; 152288 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Steinbach, Haim, undated; 152287 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Tzaig, Uri, undated; 152286 (Folder 5 Left)
  - Warren, Rosanna, undated; 152285 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Winokur, Neil, undated; 152284 (Folder 4 Left, Folder 1)
  - Wojnarowicz, David, undated; 152283 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Z[inlin], undated; 152282 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Group Exhibitions, undated; 152281 (Box 69)
  - Group Exhibitions, 198468 (Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous: Photo Portrait of F. Moore, undated; 152280 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Oversize Materials: Series III.A: Correspondence, 152275
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series III.A: Correspondence
  - AIDS Treatment Project, 1991; 152278 (Box 69)
  - Contemporary Arts Center, undated; 152277 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Leibowitz, Cary, 1994-1995; 152276 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.A: Magazines, 152272
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.A: Magazines
  - Hoard's Dairyman, 1992-1995; 152274 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Hoard's Dairyman, 1995-1996; 152273 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.B: Catalogues and Manuals, 152270
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.B: Catalogues and Manuals
  - Decor: Moulding and Supply, undated; 152271 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.C: Clippings, Articles and Subject Files, 152267
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.C: Clippings, Articles and Subject Files
  - Cowboys, 1998; 152269 (Folder 2 Right)
  - Treaty Oak, 1995-1997; 152268 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.D: Images, 152259
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.D: Images
  - Ken Brown Wrapping Paper, undated; 152266 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - DNA Cup, ink jet on foam board [located in map case], undated; 152265 (Folder 1)
  - East Asian Flower Painting, undated; 152264 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - "Emigrants" images, gridded, undated; 152263 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Images, undated; 152262 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Niagara Images, undated; 152261 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Wallpaper, 1999; 152260 (Box 69)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.E: Photographs, 152257
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.E: Photographs
  - Panoramic Photographs of Niagara Falls, undated; 152258 (Folder 1 Right)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.F: Ephemera, 152253
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.F: Ephemera
  - Birds to Color by Number, undated; 152256 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Deep in the Rockies scrapbook, undated; 152255 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Paper Dolls, undated; 152254 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.G: Books, 152247
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.G: Books
  - The Original Watercolor Paintings by John James Audobon for The Birds of America, 1966; 152252 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - The National Audubon Society Collection, North American Trees, 1984; 152251 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Doubilet, David, Pacific: An undersea journey, 1992; 152250 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Geist, Valerius, Buffalo Nation: History and legend of the North America Bison, 1996; 152249 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Wolberg, Lewis R., Micro-Art: Art images in a hidden world, undated; 152248 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Oversize Materials: Series V.D: Production Materials, Boston Ballet and Cornell University Theater, 152244
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series V.D: Production Materials, Boston Ballet and Cornell University Theater
  - Boston Ballet Repertory Lights, sound and stage plots [located in map case], undated; 152246 (Folder 3)
  - Cornell University Theater Map [located in map case], undated; 152245 (Folder 4)
- Oversize Materials: Series V.E: Promotional Materials, 152239
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series V.E: Promotional Materials
  - Beehive Posters, French Production, additional larger posters in map case, undated; 152243 (Folder 5)
  - Boston Ballet Posters, undated; 152242 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Sightlines: A Publication of the Boston Ballet, undated; 152241 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Beehive Performance Posters, 1991 Dance Concert at Cornell University, 152240 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Oversize Materials: Series V.F: Artifacts, 152237
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series V.F: Artifacts
  - Study for Hand and Forearm, undated; 152238 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Oversize Materials: Series VI.C: Miller's Wife Production Materials, 152234
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series VI.C: Miller's Wife Production Materials
  - Realty Newspapers, 1988; 152236 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Time Chart, undated; 152235 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Oversize Materials: Series VIII.A: Personal Items, 152226
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series VIII.A: Personal Items
  - X-rays, foot and toes, 1977; 152233 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - X-rays, chest and lungs, 1977; 152232 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - X-rays, lungs and chest, 1977, 1978; 152231 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - X-rays, chest, 1977; 152230 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - X-rays, chest, 1978; 152229 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - X-rays, chest, 1979; 152228 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - X-rays, nasal bones, 1980; 152227 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Oversize Materials: Series VIII.B: Art Implements and Artifacts, 152213
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series VIII.B: Art Implements and Artifacts
  - Acetate cutouts, undated; 152225 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Acetates used in "Arena", 1992; 152224 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Acetate #19, used in "Debutante" [located in map case], 1992; 152223 (Folder 12)
  - Acetate #20 used in "Clinical Trial" and "Debutante", 1991; 152222 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Acetate #21, used in "Debutante", 1992; 152221 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Acetates used in "Eclipse" and rectal pear cutouts. Group envelope #3 and Acetates #25, undated; 152220 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Layout Boards and Transparencies for Unidentified Works, undated (Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Rectal pear, undated; 152219 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Opaque material, undated; 152218 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Publicity photo and acetates, undated; 152217 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Rub on lettering, undated; 152216 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Smoke prints, undated; 152215 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Stencils, grapes, orange, semi-circle, undated; 152214 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Oversize Materials: Series VIII.C: Miscellaneous, 152211
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series VIII.C: Miscellaneous
  - Paper fragments found at the World Trade Center, September 13, 2001, 152212 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Oversize Materials: Series IX.A: Juvenalia, 152209
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IX.A: Juvenalia
  - Yale Diploma, 1975; 152210 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.A: Brochures, Merchandise Catalogues, and Owner's Manuals., 152207
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.A: Brochures, Merchandise Catalogues, and Owner's Manuals.
  - La Passion du Christ, 1975; 152208 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.B: Catalogues, 152204
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.B: Catalogues
  - Sagacho Exhibit Space, Dui Seid, 1994; 152206 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - American Fashion Awards, 2000; 152205 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.C: Periodicals, 152195
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.C: Periodicals
  - East Village Eye, April 1984, 152203 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - National Campaign for Freedom of Expression Bulletin(summer 1994), 152202 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - New York Native, #408 (11 February 1991), 152201 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - New York Times, September 12, 2001, 152200 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge for Lifetime Learning and Eduction. Vol. 32 Walt Disney., 1959; 152199 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge for Lifetime Learning and Eduction. Vol. 34 Nehru of India., 1960; 152198 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge for Lifetime Learning and Eduction. Vol. 36 John Harvard., 1961; 152197 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge for Lifetime Learning and Eduction. Vol. 38 Robert Frost., 1962; 152196 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.D: Miscellaneous, 152189
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.D: Miscellaneous
  - ACT UP poster, undated; 152194 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Bernard Mathys, undated; 152193 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Giorno, John, undated (Folder 13)
  - "No Trifling with Love", poster. Play by Alfred de Musset. Directed and Produced by Rudy Laurent., undated; 152192 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Penny Arcade publicity poster for event at PS 122, dedicated to Cookie Mueller. July 12-15, undated; 152191 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Placemat from a Japanese restaurant in France, French-Japanese translations., undated; 152190 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.E: Books, 152176
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.E: Books
  - Form and Colour: The Mosque of Cordoba, undated; 152188 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Avedon, Richard Photographs 1947-1977, 1978; 152187 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Breeskin, Adelyn Mary Cassatt advertisement and proposal for a Catalogue raisonne, undated; 152186 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Damisch, Hubert and Henry Martin Adami, 1974; 152185 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Daniel, Howard, Heronimus Bosch, 1947; 152184 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Day, F. Holland Suffering the Ideal, 1995; 152183 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Daumien, undated; 152182 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Jeff Greenfield, Television: The First Fifty Years, 1977; 152181 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Martini, Simon, Pinacoteca de los Genios, undated; 152180 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Great Moments of Harper's Bazaar, undated; 152179 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Souls Grown Deep: African American Vernacular Art of the South, vol. 1, undated; 152178 (Box 66)